Guide to the Trade catalogs collection.
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- C
  - Clipper Company (New Milford, Conn.), 1871; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4300)
    "Clipper" plow
  - Clover Manufacturing Company (Norwalk, Conn.), 1944–1950; Uai +C625; 2 volumes (Box 49, Folder 656)
    Clover abrasives
  - Clow, James B., and Sons (Chicago, Ill.), 1927; Uai C626; 2 volumes (Box 49, Folder 657)
    "Gasteam" radiators
  - Clucas and Boddington Company (New York, N.Y.), 1900; Uai +C627; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 658)
  - Cluett, Peabody and Company, Inc. (Troy, N.Y.), 1936; Uai C628; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 659)
    "Arrow" shirts, Collars, etc.
  - Coal Carburetor Company (New Brunswick, N.J.), 1937; Uai C63; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 660)
    Automatic heating equipment
  - Coatesville Boiler Works (Coatesville, Pa.), 1900; Uai +C632; 2 volumes (Box 49, Folder 661)
    Boilers, Steel tanks, Steel plate work, etc.
  - Cobb-Macey-Dohme, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1915–1923; Uai +C634; 3 volumes (Box 49, Folder 662)
    Desks, Metal cabinets, etc.
  - Codman and Shurtleff (Boston, Mass.), undated; Uai +C648; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 663)
    Invalid chairs
  - Coe and Wilkes (Painesville, Ohio), 1941; Uai C651; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 664)
    Veneer machines
  - Cold Storage Refrigerator Company (Eau Claire, Wis.), 1907; Uai C673; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 665)
    "Cold storage" refrigerators
  - Coldwell Lawn Mower Company (Newburgh, N.Y.), 1917–1929; Uai C674; 3 volumes (Box 49, Folder 666)
    Lawn mowers
  - Collins Company (Collinsville, Conn.), 1923; Uai C697; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 668)
    Axes, Hatchets, Hammers, etc.
  - Collins Company (Collinsville, Conn.), 1935; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4301)
    Axes, machetes, and edge tools
  - Collins Radio Company (Cedar Rapids, Iowa, New York, N.Y., etc.), 1939; Uai +C698; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 669)
    Broadcast transmitter
  - Collins, Warren E., Inc. (Boston, Mass.), 1931–1937; Uai +C696; 18 volumes (Box 49, Folder 667)
    Respiration apparatus
  - Colonial Blower Company (Hartford, Conn.), undated; Uai +C712; 3 volumes (Box 49, Folder 670)
    Industrial dust collectors
  - Colonial Steel Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1912–1920; Uai C715; 2 volumes (Box 49, Folder 671)
    Tool steels, etc.
  - Colonial Works Company (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1941; Uai C716; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 672)
  - Colorado Tent and Awning Company (Denver, Colo.), 1905; Uai +C719; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 673)
    Tents, Awnings, Camping equipment, etc.
  - Colt's Patent Fire Arms Manufacturing Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1935–1940; Uai +C7214; 9 volumes (Box 49, Folder 676-679)
    Fire arms
  - Colt, J.B., and Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1897; Uai +C721; 7 volumes (Box 49, Folder 674)
    Lantern slides, Gas generators, etc.
  - Colt, J.B., and Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1900; Uai +C7211; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 675)
    Stereopticons and accessories
  - Columbia Conserve Company (Indianapolis, Ind.), 1930; Uai C7218; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 680)
    Canned soups, etc.
  - Columbia Incandescent Lamp Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1894–1899; Uai +C722; 7 volumes (Box 49, Folder 681)
    Incandescent lamps
  - Columbia Phonograph Company (New York, N.Y.), 1902–1934; Uai C723; 4 volumes (Box 49, Folder 682)
    Graphophone records
  - Columbia School Furniture Corporation (Indianapolis, Ind.), 1934; Uai +C7238; 2 volumes (Box 49, Folder 683)
    "Sani-steel" desks, etc.
  - Columbia School Supply Company (Indianapolis, Ind.), 1904–1931; Uai +C724; 3 volumes (Box 49, Folder 684)
    School furniture, Laboratory supplies, etc.
  - Columbia Steel and Shafting Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1913; Uai C725; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 685)
    Shafting sand cold-finished steels
  - Columbian Rope and Twine Company (Auburn, N.Y.), 1919; Uai C726; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 686)
    Rope and twine
  - Columbus Dental Manufacturing Company (Columbus, Ohio), undated; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4302)
    Dental tools
  - Columbus Iron Works Company (Columbus, Ga.), undated; Uai +C7266; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 687)
    "Raoul" journal box
  - Combination Ladder Company (New York, N.Y., Providence, R.I.), 1937; Uai C733; 1 volume (Box 49, Folder 688)
    Fire ladders
  - Comerford, N.J. (Joliet, Ill.), 1928; Uai +C734; 2 volumes (Box 50, Folder 689)
    Audible warning signals
  - Common Brick Manufacturers' Association of America (Cleveland, Ohio), 1924; Uai C737; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 690)
    Brick homes
  - Compañia Compensadora del Trabjo (Havana, Cuba), 1931; Uai C738; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 691)
    Cigars
  - Compressed Gas Manufacturers' Association (New York, N.Y.), 1926–1927; Uai +C74; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 692)
    Compressed gas, etc.
  - Comstock, Wm. G. (East Hartford, Conn.), 1869; Uai +C7403; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 693)
    Horticultural implements
  - Condit, Hanson and Van Winkle (Newark, N.J.), 1879; Uai +C753; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 694)
    Nickel and electro-plating material
  - Congoleum-Nairn Inc. (Kearny, N.J.), 1941; Uai +C761; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 695)
    Linoleum
  - Conklin, T.E., Brass and Copper Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1940–1951; Uai C7614; 4 volumes (Box 50, Folder 696-698)
    Nuts, Bolts, Tubes, etc.
  - Connecticut Adamant Plaster Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1902; Uai C762; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 699)
    Adamant wall plaster
  - Connecticut Telephone and Electric Corporation (Meriden, Conn.), undated; Uai +C7265; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 701)
    Telephone and signal systems
  - Connor, W.B., Engineering Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1940; Uai +C7624; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 700)
    Dorex odor absorbers
  - Conroy, Prugh and Company (Allegheny, Pa.), undated; Uai C763; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 702)
    Mirrors
  - Consolidated Aircraft Corporation (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1931; Uai +C7663; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 703)
    Consolidated Husky Junior aircraft
  - Consolidated Ashcroft Hancock Company, Inc. (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1935–1936; Uai +C7664; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 704)
    Ashcroft American gauges
  - Consolidated Car-Heating Company (Albany, N.Y.), 1890–1904; Uai +C7665; 4 volumes (Box 50, Folder 705-707)
    Car heating systems and parts
  - Consolidated Instrument Company of America (New York, N.Y.), 1921; Uai +C7668; 2 volumes (Box 50, Folder 708)
    Speed indicators, Laboratory centrifuges
  - Consolidated Safety Valve Company (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1898–1910; Uai C7675; 2 volumes (Box 50, Folder 709)
    "Pop" safety valves
  - Container Corporation of America (Chicago, Ill.), 1942; Uai +C7678; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 710)
    Paperboard containers
  - Continental Car-Na-Var Corporation (Brazil, Ind.), 1937; Uai +C768; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 711)
    Floor wax
  - Continental Cotton Gin Company (Atlanta, Ga., etc.), 1927; Uai +C76812; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 713)
    Continental cotton ginning machinery
  - Continental Fibre Company (Newark, Del.), 1944–1946; Uai C7681; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 712)
    Vulcanized fiber
  - Continental Iron Works (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1895–1898; Uai C7682; 2 volumes (Box 50, Folder 714-715)
    Suspension furnaces
  - Continental Laboratory Specialties Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1926–1930; Uai +C7683; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 716)
    Laboratory equipment for chemistry, biology, etc.
  - Continental Motors Corporation (Detroit, Mich.), 1932; Uai +C7685; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 717)
    Divco milk delivery vehicles
  - Continental Steel Corporation, Kokomo Steel and Wire Company (Kokomo, Ind.), 1928–1929; Uai C769; 2 volumes (Box 50, Folder 718)
    Fences
  - Coogan, Jas. J., and Brothers (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai C771; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 719)
    Furniture, etc.
  - Cook, G. and D., and Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1860; Uai C772; 1 volume (Box 398)
    Carriages, etc.
  - Cooke and Cobb Company (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1915; Uai +C775; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 720)
    Stationary binders
  - Cookson, Isaac, and Company (Newcastle-upon-Tyne, England), 1845; Uai C776; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 721)
    Unsilvered glass plates
  - Cooper Hewitt Electric Company (New York, N.Y.), 1927; Uai C788; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 726)
    Mercury vapor lamps
  - Cooper, Wm. S., Brass Works (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1894–1898; Uai +C786; 12 volumes (Box 75)
    Bathroom plumbing, etc.
  - Cooper-Bessemer Corporation (Mt. Vernon, Ohio, etc.), 1936–1946; Uai +C787; 24 volumes (Box 50, Folder 722-725)
    Engines
  - Cope and Maxwell Manufacturing Company (Hamilton, Ohio), undated; Uai +C79; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 727)
    Hydraulic machinery
  - Coppus Engineering and Equipment Company (Worcester, Mass.), 1919; Uai C796; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 728)
    Boilers, Pumps, etc.
  - Corbett and Peele, Perseverance Iron Works (Shrewsbury, England), 1878; Uai +C811; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 729)
    Farm machinery
  - Corbin, P. and F. (New Britain, Conn.), Uai +C812
    Locks, Hardware for doors, etc.
    - 1895–1926, 6 volumes (Box 76)
    - 1876, 1 volume (Box 77)
    - 1895, 1 volume (Box 78)
  - Cordley and Hayes (New York, N.Y.), 1890; Uai +C813; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 730)
    Fiber ware
  - Corey, Francis W. and Company (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai C8135; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 731)
    Portable track and cars
  - Corliss Carbon Company (Bradford, Pa.), 1944–1946; Uai C814; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 732)
    Corliss carbon brushes
  - Cornell, J.B. and J.M., Company (New York, N.Y.), 1904; Uai C815; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 733)
    Metallic furniture
  - Cortland Corundum Wheel Company (Cortland, N.Y.), 1923; Uai C818; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 734)
    Corundum wheel
  - Cory, Chas., and Son, Inc. (New York, N.Y., etc.), 1923–1925; Uai +C819; 2 volumes (Box 58, Folder 798-799)
    Signaling, communicating, and lighting equipment, Seamless metal hose
  - Cosgrove's (New Haven, Conn.), 1901; Uai C821; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 735)
  - Costello, J.S., and Son, Brush Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1916; Uai C824; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 736)
    Janitor supplies, Brushes, etc.
  - Cotrell and Leonard (Albany, N.Y.), undated; Uai C826; 2 volumes (Box 50, Folder 737)
    Caps and gowns
  - Couffield, H.L., Company (Grand Rapids, Mich.), 1927; Uai C831; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 738)
    Sectional files
  - Coughlin, P. (Prescott, Ontario, Canada), 1881; Uai C832; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 739)
    Iron fence posts
  - Coulter and McKenzie Machine Company (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1946; Uai C833; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 740)
    Oyster industry
  - Coutant, L. (Ivry, France), 1875; Uai C837; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 741)
    Special iron works
  - Coventry Machinists' Company, Ltd., U.S. Branch (Boston, Mass.), 1885–1888; Uai +C838; 2 volumes (Box 50, Folder 742)
    Bicycles and tricycles
  - Cox and Stevens (New York, N.Y.), 1926–1946; Uai +C8413; 3 volumes (Box 50, Folder 746)
    Yachts
  - Cox, A.M.R. (London, England), undated; Uai C8396; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 744)
    Marezzo marble
  - Cox, Sons, Buckley, and Company (New York, N.Y., London, England), undated; Uai +C841; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 745)
    Church furniture, Fabrics, Embroidery, etc.
  - Coxhead, Ralph C., Corporation (New York, N.Y.), 1934; Uai +C842; 1 volume (Box 50, Folder 747)
    "Mathematon" automatic mathematician
  - Crane Company (Chicago, Ill.), Uai +C851; 12 volumes
    Valves and fittings
    - 1900–1917, 7 volumes (Box 59, Folder 800-803)
    - 1923–1934, 4 volumes (Box 60, Folder 804-805)
    - 1906, 1 volume (Box 61)
  - Crane, Z., and W.M., Inc. (Dalton, Mass.), 1938; Uai C850; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 748)
    Engraved stationary
  - Creek Chub Bait Company (Garret, Ind.), 1928; Uai C861; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 749)
    Nature lures and tackle
  - Creosoted Wood Paving Block Bureau (Chicago, Ill.), 1915; Uai C862; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 750)
    Creosoted wood block pavements
  - Crerar, Adams and Company (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai +C863; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 751)
    Railway supplies, Contractors' materials
  - Crescent Corporation (Fall River, Mass.), 1949; Uai C8638; 6 volumes (Box 51, Folder 752-754)
    Machinery, Equipment, Supplies, etc.
  - Crescent Machine Company (Leetonia, Ohio), 1912; Uai +C864; 2 volumes (Box 51, Folder 755)
    Wood-working machinery
  - Crocker-Wheeler Electric Company (New York, N.Y.), 1894–1898; Uai +C871; 2 volumes (Box 51, Folder 756)
    Electric power company
  - Crooker Mantel and Tile Company (Providence, R.I., etc.), undated; Uai C882; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 757)
    Wood mantels, Fireplaces, Parquetry floors, Grille and fretwork, etc.
  - Crosby Steam Gage and Valve Company (Boston, Mass., etc.), 1893–1909; Uai +C884; 7 volumes (Box 51, Folder 758-759)
    Crosby indicators and recording equipment
  - Crouse-Hinds Electric Company (Syracuse, N.Y.), Uai +C885
    Electrical materials
    - 1900–1935, 15 volumes (Box 62, Folder 806-813)
    - 1949, 1 volume (Box 63)
  - Crowe Metal Manufacturing Company (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai C8857; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 760)
    Metal advertising cards, etc.
  - Crowell Apparatus Company (Indianapolis, Ind.), undated; Uai C886; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 761)
  - Crown Novelty Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1914; Uai +C888; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 762)
    Gas and electric portable lamps
  - Crownshield, B.B., (Boston, Mass., New York, N.Y.), 1906; Uai +C8885; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 763)
  - Crucible Steel Company of America (Pittsburgh, Pa.), 1911–1923; Uai C891; 5 volumes (Box 51, Folder 764-765)
    Steel works
  - Cullen, Martin J., (Denver, Colo.), undated; Uai C897; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 766)
    Seeds, Plants, Bulbs, etc.
  - Cullman Wheel Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1912; Uai C898; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 767)
    Steel sprockets, Diamond chains
  - Cunningham Company (Boston, Mass.), 1884; Uai +C917; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 768)
    Bicycles, Tricycles, etc.
  - Curtain Supply Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1911; Uai +C94; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 769)
    Car curtains
  - Curtis Lighting, Inc. (Chicago, Ill., etc.), 1924; Uai +C947; 3 volumes (Box 51, Folder 772)
    Lighting fixtures, X-ray reflectors, etc.
  - Curtis Manufacturing Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1937–1938; Uai +C948; 4 volumes (Box 51, Folder 773)
    Air conditioning units, Dental pumps, etc.
  - Curtis and Company Manufacturing Company (St. Louis, Mo.), 1911; Uai +C942; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 770)
    Pneumatic appliances
  - Curtis and Curtis (Bridgeport, Conn.), 1893; Uai +C943; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 771)
    Pipe cutting and threading machinery
  - Curtiss-Robertson Airplane Manufacturing Company, 1928; Uai +C949; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 774)
  - Cushman Chuck Company (Hartford, Conn.), 1908–1914; Uai C959; 4 volumes (Box 51, Folder 776)
    "Cushman" chucks
  - Cushman and Denison Manufacturing Company (New York, N.Y.), 1910; Uai C958; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 775)
    Office supplies
  - Cutler-Hammer Manufacturing Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1913–1939; Uai +C971; 39 volumes (Box 51, Folder 777)
    Controllers and other electrical apparatus
  - Cutter Electrical and Manufacturing Company (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1911; Uai C9825; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 779)
    Circuit breakers
  - Cutter, George, Company (South Bend, Ind.), 1916–1918; Uai +C982; 3 volumes (Box 51, Folder 778)
    Electrical lighting fixtures and wiring devices
  - Cutter, J.H., and Company, undated; Uai +C983; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 780)
    Ice tools
  - Cyclone Fence Company, 1946; Uai +C991; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 781)
  - Cyclone Grate-Bar Company (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1946; Uai C993; 1 volume (Box 51, Folder 787)
    Shaking and dumping grate
  - Cyphers Incubator Company (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1903–1912; Uai C992; 5 volumes (Box 51, Folder 782-786)
    Incubators
- D
  - D and W Fuse Company (Providence, R.I), 1906; Uai D115; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 814)
    Fuses and safety devices
  - D'Andrea Brothers (New York, N.Y., London, England), 1940; Uai D197; 2 volumes (Box 79, Folder 824)
    Men's suits
  - Da-Lite Screen Company, Inc. (Chicago, Ill.), 1941; Uai +D16; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 821)
    "Electrol" screens
  - Daemicke, Paul J. (Chicago, Ill.), 1893; Uai +D129; 2 volumes (Box 79, Folder 815)
    Butchers' and packers' tools and supplies
  - Dagincourt and Cie (Paris, France), 1890; Uai D133; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 816)
    Minerals, Microscopes, etc.
  - Daigger, A. (Chicago, Ill.), undated; Uai D14; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 817)
  - Daimler Company Limited (Coventry, England), 1938; Uai +D1428; 2 volumes (Box 85)
  - Dairy and Ice Cream Machinery and Supplies Association, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1928–1931; Uai +D147; 2 volumes (Box 79, Folder 818)
    Dairy machinery, etc.
  - Dairymen's Supply Company, Inc. (Philadelphia, Pa.), undated; Uai D148; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 819)
  - Dalifol, A. (Paris, France), 1878; Uai +D159; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 820)
    Malleable iron and steel
  - Dallons Laboratories (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1942; Uai +D173; 2 volumes (Box 79, Folder 822)
    Ultraviolet generators
  - Dalton Shoe Company (Dalton, Mass.), undated; Uai D175; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 823)
    Jenness Miller shoes
  - Darley. W.S. and Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1949; Uai +D247; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 825)
    Police supplies
  - Davids, Thaddeus, Company (New York, N.Y.), 1911; Uai +D281; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 826)
    Inks, Sealing wax, etc.
  - Davis Milk Machinery Company (North Chicago, Ill.), 1917; Uai +D31; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 831)
    Milk machinery
  - Davis Sewing Machine Company (Dayton, Ohio), 1892–1894; Uai +D312a; 6 volumes (Box 79, Folder 832)
    Sewing machines
  - Davis Sewing Machine Company (Dayton, Ohio), 1897–1901; Uai +D312; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 833)
    "Dayton" bicycles
  - Davis and Egan Machine Tool Company (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1896; Uai D292; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 827)
  - Davis, G.M., Regulator Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1910; Uai +D293; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 828)
  - Davis, R.B., Company (Hoboken, N.J.), 1939; Uai D297; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 829)
    Cocomalt
  - Davis, W.P., Machine Company (Rochester, N.Y.), 1912; Uai D299; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 830)
    Keyseating and keyways
  - Davis-Watkins Dairymen's Manufacturing Company (Jersey City, N.J., etc.), 1918; Uai +D313; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 834)
    "Disbrow" churns, etc.
  - Davol Rubber Company (Providence, R.I.), 1947; Uai +D325; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 835)
    Hospital supplies
  - Dawson Brothers (Chicago, Ill.), 1905; Uai D328; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 836)
    Eclipse gas grates
  - Day and Night Water Heater Company, Ltd. (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1940; Uai +D333; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 837)
    Storage coolers
  - Dayton Rubber Manufacturing Company (Dayton, Ohio), 1936; Uai +D338; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 839)
    V-belts
  - Dayton, G.S., and Company (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +D337; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 838)
    Sporting goods
  - De Groff, Lewis, and Son (New York, N.Y.), 1911; Uai D363; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 846)
    Health brand food products
  - De La Vergne Machine Company (New York, N.Y.), 1924–1927; Uai +D3768; 4 volumes (Box 79, Folder 855-856)
  - De Laval Separator Company (New York, N.Y.), 1891–1905; Uai +D375; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 852)
    Cream separators
  - De Laval's, G., Steam Turbine Works (Stockholm, Sweden), undated; Uai +D3761; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 854)
    Steam turbines
  - De Luxe Saddlery Company (Baltimore, Md.), 1946; Uai D389; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 862)
    Saddlery, Riding apparel
  - De laval Steam Turbine Company (Trenton, N.J.), 1912; Uai +D376; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 853)
  - DeForest and Hotchkiss Company (New Haven, Conn.), 1946; Uai +D362; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 845)
    Building materials
  - DeHaven Manufacturing Company (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1913; Uai D366; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 847)
    Shipping supplies
  - Decorah Windmill Company (Decorah, Iowa), 1893; Uai +D358; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 840)
    Steel windmills and towers
  - Deere, John, 1937–1946; Uai +D36; 2 volumes (Box 79, Folder 841-842)
    Farm equipment
  - Deering, Wm., and Company (Chicago, Ill.), 1893; Uai +D361; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 843-844)
    Farm implements, Harvesting machinery, etc.
  - Deimal Linen-Mesh Company (New York, N.Y., San Francisco, Calif.), 1942; Uai D368; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 848)
    Underwear
  - Dejonge, Louis, and Company (New York, N.Y., etc.), undated; Uai D369; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 849)
    Coated book paper
  - Delagrave, Charles (Paris, France), 1888–1889; Uai +D372; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 850)
  - Delamater Iron Works (New York, N.Y.), 1881; Uai +D373; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 851)
    Caloric pumping Engine
  - Deleuil et Fils (Paris, France), 1856–1865; Uai D378; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 857-859)
    Chemistry and physics instruments, etc.
  - Delphos Can Company (Delphos, Ohio), Uai D386; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 860)
    Oil cans, Factory dispensers, Tanks, etc.
  - Delta Manufacturing Company (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1934–1941; Uai +D388; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 861)
    Power tools
  - Demarest, C.B., and Company (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1891; Uai +D392; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 863)
    Folding chairs
  - Demco Library Supplies (Madison, Wis., New Haven, Conn.), undated; Uai +D3935; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 864)
    Library supplies
  - Demond and Brown Chair Company (Winchendon, Mass.), 1923; Uai D397; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 865)
    Chairs
  - Demorest, Madame (New York, N.Y.), 1876–1877; 1 volume (Box 399, Folder 4304)
    Clothing, etc.
  - Dennison and Sons (New York, N.Y.), 1923; Uai +D425; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 866)
    Stationary supplies
  - Dent, E., and Company (London, England), undated; Uai D435; 1 volume (Box 79, Folder 867)
    Clocks, Watches, etc.
  - Dentinol and Pyorrhocide Company (New York, N.Y.), 1914; Uai +D436; 2 volumes (Box 79, Folder 868)
    Oral hygiene
  - Derby Desk Company (Boston, Mass.), 1906–1913; Uai +D445; 6 volumes (Box 80, Folder 870-873)
  - Derby, P., and Company (New York, N.Y.), 1903–1905; Uai +D444; 3 volumes (Box 79, Folder 869)
    Go-carts, Baby carriages, etc.
  - Derbyshire, F.W. (Waltham, Mass.), 1912; Uai +D446; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 874)
    Lathes, etc.
  - Derge, Otto (Berlin, Germany), 1881; Uai D447; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 875)
    Optical instruments
  - Desaga, P. (Heidelberg, Germany), 1862–1867; Uai +D451; 5 volumes (Box 80, Folder 876-877)
    Bunsen burners, Chemical apparatus
  - Deschiens (Paris, France), 1939; Uai D454; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 878)
    Deschiens' syrup
  - Despatch Manufacturing Company (Minneapolis, Minn.), 1911; Uai D467; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 879)
    Electric ovens
  - Detroit Fuse and Manufacturing Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1917–1923; Uai D482; 4 volumes (Box 80, Folder 880)
    Fuses, Electrical safety devices, etc.
  - Detroit Heating and Lighting Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1892; Uai +D483; 3 volumes (Box 80, Folder 881)
    Hot water heaters, Gasoline lighting systems
  - Detroit Rex Products Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1936; Uai +D4837; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 882)
    Metal cleaning supplies
  - Detroit Sanitary Supply Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1898; Uai +D484; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 883)
    Plumbing supplies
  - Detroit Stove Works (Detroit, Mich.), 1876–1916; Uai +D4846; 3 volumes (Box 86)
    "Jewel" gas stoves
  - Detroit Twist Drill Company (Detroit, Mich.), 1923; Uai D485; 2 volumes (Box 80, Folder 884)
    Drills, Reamers, Cutters, etc.
  - Deutsche Elektrizitäts-Werke (Aachen, Germany), 1894–1896; Uai +D489; 3 volumes (Box 80, Folder 885)
    Electric motors, Dynamos, etc.
  - Devine, J.P., Company (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1921; Uai +D496; 2 volumes (Box 80, Folder 886)
    Vacuum drying apparatus, etc.
  - Devoe and Raynolds Company, Inc. (New York, N.Y.), 1918; Uai D497; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 887)
  - Dewey and Johnson (New York, N.Y.), undated; Uai +D516; 1 volume (Box 80, Folder 889)